hello,
all good?
good? macaw,
half a day right?
Are you on time or not?
What time did I decide?
can start?
IS. it's eleven.
it's two minutes.
Is everything okay?
is what not.
about maintenance.
oh,
let me call.
It's good?
thanks.
is that I am always late.
I'm already justifying myself when I'm on time.
do you have an ID?
I fall,
I have what do you want my RG?
no? from the mall
people didn't pass you?
no. no,
no longer out of concept
don't you have a maintenance to do today?
not sure about the concept?
I'm crazy.
let me explain.
I came here to fix your day.
I'm Caio from the workshop
of the Passenger
and this chocolate ball here
contains twenty grams of happiness.
Diana,
oh that's legal,
how much happiness you need on your day today.
congratulations!
thank you son,
too good, right?
,
I spent the night making a Brigadier.
how good I am happy.
I won't do no.
thank you
that was 1 joke
and good sales to you tomorrow.
all good.
thanks.
it was!
good sales there.
thanks.
bye,